cusp.com 2012-04-21

# CUSP | Security & Privacy

##### Security & Privacy

  * Security & privacy information
  * Browser advisory
  * Warranty information
  * Conditions of use, notices and disclaimers
  * Protecting Yourself from Internet Scams

##### Introduction

This web site ("Web Site") is operated by CUSP, a division of the Neiman Marcus Group, Inc ("CUSP" or "we" or "us"). This privacy policy only covers information collected at this Web Site, and does not cover any information collected offline by Neiman Marcus (unless specifically stated).

##### Security 

Personal information provided on the Web Site and online credit card transactions are transmitted through a secure server using Secure Socket Layering (SSL), encryption technology. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area.

You may purchase online merchandise by calling toll-free 1-800-401-2101—24 hours a day, seven days a week. One of our customer care associates will gladly take your order. 

We are committed to handling your personal information with high standards of information security. We take appropriate physical, electronic and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Our website uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. Our customer care center and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

##### Privacy policy 

To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers, as well as from other parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have implemented procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe, secure, and responsible manner. 

We have posted this privacy policy in order to explain our information collection practices and the choices you have about the way information is collected and used. 

As we continue to develop our Web site and take advantage of advances in technology to improve the services we offer, this privacy policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 3, 2005.

##### The information we collect 

Generally, you may browse the Web Site without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this Web Site. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access all of this Web Site or participate in all of its features.

We receive and store any personally identifiable information you enter on the Web Site, whenever you shop with Neiman Marcus -- online, through or catalogs, or in our stores, or information you give us in any other way. For example, we may collect the following personally identifiable information: your name, address, telephone number, driver's license number, birth date, and e-mail address. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, we will also include your account number. 

When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite designers.

If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our promotions or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences.

From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.

When you visit this Web Site, our web server automatically collect anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer care, and special promotions. 

##### How we use the information we collect 

We use the information we collect for various purposes, including: 

  * to complete your purchase transactions
  * to provide the services you request 
  * to send you our catalogs and other offerings by mail
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer care, and overall shopping experience

##### Others with whom we share your information

The Neiman Marcus Group: All of the above information that we collect, as described above, may be shared among all Neiman Marcus entities, including Neiman Marcus, Horchow and Bergdorf Goodman. 

Service providers: We also may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing e-mails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide us storage and analysis; (d) provide fraud prevention; and (e) other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep confidential all information we share with them and to use the information only to perform their obligations in the agreements.

Other companies: We may provide information to carefully selected outside companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you.

Business Transitions: We may transfer or share a copy of personal information about you in the event that CUSP or its parent, one of its properties, affiliates or subsidiaries, goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our web site prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal information, if your personal information will be used contrary to this policy. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of Neiman Marcus to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever. Neiman Marcus specifically reserves the right to transfer or share a copy of personally identifiable information collected from its websites to the buyer of that portion of its business relating to that information.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors of this Web Site or the public.

##### Your choices regarding use of the information we collect

We provide you with a number of choices regarding our handling of your nonpublic personally identifiable information.

Direct Mail or Telephone Marketing: If you shop at the Neiman Marcus or Bergdorf Goodman stores and wish to be removed from the list of customers that receive direct mail or telemarketing calls, please either:

  * write to: Neiman Marcus Customer Relations at P.O. Box 650589, Dallas, Texas, 75265-0589

or call toll-free at 1-800-401-2101 

If you choose to write to us, please include your name, address and credit card account number (if you have one), and state one of the following: 

  * “NO MAIL OFFERS” (if you don’t want to receive offers by mail); 
  * “NO PHONE OFFERS” (if you don’t want to receive offers by phone); or 
  * “NO PHONE OR MAIL OFFERS” (if you don’t want to receive either).

Because customer lists often are prepared well in advance of an offering (sometimes few months before the offer is made), you may continue to receive some offers after you send us a request not to use your information for specified marketing purposes. We appreciate your patience and understanding in giving us time to carry out your request. 

Please note that we do not offer an opt out from sharing nonpublic personally identifiable information about you among Neiman Marcus Group entities.

##### Your California Privacy Rights 

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Neiman Marcus Customer Relations, P.O.Box 650589, Dallas, Texas 75265-0589. Please allow 30 days for a response. 

##### Cookies, Web Beacons, and how we use them

A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) upon entering our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database. A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer to a website. 

We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the Web Site as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the Web site you visited immediately before clicking to NeimanMarcus.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our Web Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. 

We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services or data management. We call them our Customer Care Partners. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Customer Care Partners. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in such services. If you would like to opt out of these services, please [click here](http://www.neimanmarcus.com/store/service/optOutPopUp.jhtml). 

##### Children’s privacy 

Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. Our Web Site is a general audience site. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web Site is targeted to attract anyone under 13. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent’s consent. Our online sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who are at least 18 years old. 

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the web. 

##### Links to other sites

While visiting CUSP.com, you may link to Web sites operated by our business partners or other third parties. This does not mean that we endorse these Web sites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any Web site you may access through this Web site. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities.

In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other sites. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not the Neiman Marcus privacy policy. Make sure you understand any Web site’s privacy policies before providing personal information. 

##### Online account registration 

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with CUSP.com. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; they will be securely stored with us for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information. 

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to LOG OUT at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer. 

##### E-mails 

You will receive promotional e-mails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receive email from Neiman Marcus or its affiliates you can click on the unsubscribe link and hit send at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Please allow us 3 business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request. 

##### Acceptance 

By using this Web Site, you accept the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

##### Any questions? 

We’ll be happy to provide additional information or answer any questions. Please:

  * Call toll-free 1-800-401-2101
  * Write:Customer Relations  
P.O. Box 650589  
Dallas, TX 75265-0589

##### Browser Advisory 

PC users should place their online order using Internet Explorer or Firefox. Macintosh users should place their online orders using Safari or Firefox. These browsers allow us to offer our customers the highest level of security; some other browsers prevent users from viewing secure pages during the checkout process. We apologize for any inconvenience. 

Download a free copy of Firefox by clicking [here](http://www.mozilla.com/firefox). For the latest version of Safari, from the Apple menu, choose Software Update. For the latest Internet Explorer version visit [here](http://windowsupdate.microsoft.com/). 

Please be aware that CUSP.com uses rich media content to improve the user experience. [Download and Install Adobe Flash](http://www.adobe.com/go/getflashplayer/) to view the website as it was intended. 

##### Warranty information

Some items on our Web site have a manufacturer’s warranty; this is noted in the product description. To obtain a written warranty for any of these items, send a specific written request to: 

Neiman Marcus  
P.O. Box 650589  
Dallas, TX 75265-0589

##### Conditions of use, notices and disclaimers

When you use this Web site, you are automatically agreeing that both your access to the site and your use of it are: 

  * Subject to the terms and conditions in this legal notice, which may change at any time without notice. 
  * Subject to all applicable laws. 
  * Undertaken at your own risk. 

Please refer to this page frequently to review our current terms and conditions of use.

##### Copyright 

The following elements of this Web site are the property of Neiman Marcus or our suppliers and are protected by United States and international copyright laws: 

  * All text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, and data compilations -- both individually and as they are compiled on the site. 
  * All software.

##### Trademarks 

The trademarks or trade dress of Neiman Marcus and our affiliates may not be used without our written permission. Trademarks or trade dress include the Neiman Marcus name and logo, and other graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts, and service names of Neiman Marcus products, services, and programs, and those of our affiliates. 

VELCRO® is a registered trademark of Velcro Industries, B.V. 

All other trademarks that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by us or our affiliates. 

##### Use 

You have permission to electronically copy and print hard copies of pages from this Web site solely for personal, non-commercial purposes related to placing an order or shopping with CUSP.com. Unless we give you written permission in advance, any other use of this Web site, its content and its information, including linking or framing to this Web site, are strictly prohibited. 

##### Errors and inaccuracies 

Our goal is to provide complete, accurate, up-to-date information on our Web site. Unfortunately, it is not possible to ensure that any Web site is completely free of human or technological errors. This site may contain typographical mistakes, inaccuracies, or omissions, some of which may relate to pricing and availability, and some information may not be complete or current. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions -- including after an order has been submitted -- and to change or update information at any time without prior notice. We sincerely apologize for any inconvenience this may cause. 

##### Disclaimer of liability 

We make no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, with respect to this Web site, its content, or the information available on or through it; they are provided “as is,” with all faults. Except as otherwise provided under applicable laws, we and our corporate affiliates, and the directors, officers, employees, agents, contractors, successors and assigns of each, will not be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or related to the use of this Web site or any other Web site linked to it. This limitation of liability applies to direct, indirect, consequential, special, punitive or other damages you or others may suffer, as well as damages for lost profits, business interruption or the loss of data or information, even if we are notified in advance of the potential for any such damages. 

##### No confidentiality 

Except for information necessary to place an order, we do not want to receive confidential or proprietary information or trade secrets through this Web site. Any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to us will be deemed non-confidential, and by submitting it, you are granting us an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute it for any purpose whatsoever, with no payment or other compensation to you. However, we will not use your name unless we are required by law to identify the source of the materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments, or unless we first obtain your permission. 

##### Applicable law 

By visiting this Web site, you agree that the laws of the state of Texas, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Conditions of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and us or any of our affiliates. 

##### Disputes 

Any dispute relating in any way to your visit to our Web site or to products purchased here shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in Dallas, Texas. However, if you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the state of Texas. You consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Any arbitration under this agreement shall be conducted under the prevailing rules of the American Arbitration Association. The arbitrator’s award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration with respect to this Web site or to products purchased here shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise. 

##### Protecting your information 

As part of our ongoing commitment to ensure that your shopping experience with CUSP.com is protected, CUSP.com will prosecute all unauthorized or fraudulent transactions to the fullest extent allowed by law.

##### Protecting Yourself from Internet Scams

It should come as no surprise that one of our highest priorities at The Neiman Marcus Group is keeping your personal information secure and confidential. To that end, we would like to share some of the most common types of Internet scams and suggestions on how you can be aware of and help protect yourself against identity theft.

##### Fictitious Job Offer Emails Alert

Email campaigns offering fictitious job offers are a reality. The emails can be quite authentic looking. They often purport to have been sent directly from one of our executives or from our human resources department. Enclosures, such as company information sheets and detailed questionnaires, may display The Neiman Marcus Group logo or the logo of one of our divisions (Neiman Marcus, Horchow, Cusp, Last Call, or Bergdorf Goodman). The emails may include a request for payment of a processing fee of several hundred dollars, and/or they may offer reimbursement for certain job-application or relocation expenses.

These emails are fraudulent. The Neiman Marcus Group does not extend job offers via email to individuals with whom it has had no prior contact. We do not ask prospective employees to pay a fee to be considered for a position or to receive a job offer. We do not authorize recruiters or agents to do any of these things on our behalf. Fraudulent job offers are an unfortunate possibility. Please be aware, as we will not honor them in any way.

You should not respond to any of these job offers by revealing personal information, nor should you send any funds in response to them. If you receive one of these fraudulent offers, please report the matter to the U.S. Secret Service. You may also email our security group at [nmhc@neimanmarcus.com](mailto:nmhc@neimanmarcus.com "nmhc@neimanmarcus.com").

##### Phishing And Spoofing Alert

This is when a criminal sends you a phony message or a Website link that appears to be from a legitimate business. They will directly request that you provide personal financial information, such as:

  * Name and address
  * Social Security numbers
  * Credit card numbers/bank account numbers
  * Pin numbers/passwords

##### Pop-Up Advertisements Alert

Some advertisements "pop up" in a separate browser window advising that you have won a contest or request that you participate in a survey to collect a prize. They may then ask that you provide personal information in order to receive your gift. By clicking on the link it is possible that you are also downloading viruses designed to capture or destroy information on your computer.

##### Check Scam Alert

A similar but low-tech scam circulates occasionally, in the form of a check, purportedly from The Neiman Marcus Group or one of our divisions, and instructions to deposit it right away, usually in order to receive the balance of a larger sum you have "won" or that has otherwise come to you unexpectedly. You will be instructed to immediately send a payment, in the form of a second personal check, wire transfer, or similar, to some third party to cover taxes, processing fees, administrative costs, or some similarly vague expense. The check you receive in the mail likely would look quite authentic and probably would have our Neiman Marcus Group trademark on it. Do not deposit the check or follow the instructions you receive with it. The check you deposit will bounce; the check you write or funds you wire will clear, before you know about the bounce, and certainly before you can stop payment on your own check.

##### Important Risk-Reducing Tips

  * Never respond to emails that cannot be verified.
  * Never provide personal information via email.
  * Contact the business by using legitimate phone numbers to verify the request.
  * Enter Websites using your browser and not by clicking on provided links.
  * Be cautious of any solicitation requesting that you deposit a check or pay a fee to collect a prize, get a job, or cover vaguely described "costs."
  * Consider filing a report with the Federal Trade Commission and/or state attorney general's consumer protection office, or the FBI. Online complaints may be filed with the FTC at <https://www.ftccomplaintassistant.gov/>, and white collar crimes may be reported to the FBI at <http://www.ic3.gov/complaint/default.aspx>.

© 2012 The Neiman Marcus Group, Inc. All rights reserved.
